#### Contact

+387603311697 (Mobile) berin.mujcinovic@edu.fit.ba

www.linkedin.com/in/berinmujcinovic (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Explorer

Music Production

Knowledge Management

# Berin Mujčinović

Software Developer at Meta Software Solutions | Student at Faculty of Information Technologies

Bosnia and Herzegovina

# Summary

Currently studying at the Faculty of Information Technologies in Mostar, Bosnia and Herzegowina.

Working at Meta Software Solutions in Mostar, Bosnia and Herzegowina.

Learning C++, C#, AngularJS, Docker, Service Management and DevOps operations.

Have experience in Digital Marketing, WordPress, Web Hosting, HTML & CSS, Javascrypt.

Volunteer in the local BEST group - BEST Mostar. Involved in HR, FR and IT Teams.

Was involved in realizing first HackAtHome event from BEST Mostar, which was later confirmed

by Event Recognition group as a First Recognized Event on International level of BEST.

Hobby - Music Production

## Experience

Meta Software Solutions

1 year 8 months

Software Developer

October 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Mostar, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bosnia and Herzegovina

DevOps Engineer

July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months)

Mostar, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bosnia and Herzegovina

The Right Street
Junior Consultant, Web & Technical

Page 1 of 2

#### August 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Mostar, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bosnia and Herzegovina

#### **BEST Mostar**

#### President

June 2020 - June 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Mostar, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bosnia and Herzegovina

#### Alviral

#### Designer

November 2019 - December 2019 (2 months)

Mostar, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bosnia and Herzegovina

### Education

Faculty of Information Technologies, University "Džemal Bijedić" in Mostar

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (October 2017 - 2023)

Royal Embassy of Saudi Arabia, Cultural Centre "King Fahd" HTML & CSS Web Design Course